<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">107410_Depth Testing</string>
    <string name="application_fail">107437_Failed to submit application.</string>
    <string name="application_nosubmitted">107436_Application not submitted</string>
    <string name="application_submitted">107435_Application submitted</string>
    <string name="apply_agree">107418_I have read and agree to the aforesaid contents.</string>
    <string name="apply_disclaimer">"158409_1. The test program may have unforeseeable impacts on the phone. If you join this test program, you shall bear the consequent risks.
2. Some functions, for example, photo taking, may not run properly, or your device may be damaged due to third-party firmware.
3. Joining the test program may cause personal and confidential information leakage, compromising system security.
4. The test program may modify some of system functions, and prevent you from updating the system to the latest version of ColorOS.
5. If you join the test program, your phone will be restored to factory defaults. Before joining the test program, back up data on your phone.
6. Once you join the test program, your phone cannot be changed or returned, but can be repaired."</string>
    <string name="apply_submit">107416_Submit Application</string>
    <string name="apply_supplement">107419_The aforesaid contents do not cover all risks that may come with depth testing. Think twice before joining the test.</string>
    <string name="apply_title">107415_Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="detail_excess">107444_The number of users applying for depth testing has reached the maximum limit.</string>
    <string name="detail_govcustom">107447_This is a government- or corporate-owned phone.</string>
    <string name="detail_invalidlogin">107449_Abnormal sign-in status</string>
    <string name="detail_logintime">107450_The activation period of your OPPO ID is less than 60 consecutive days.</string>
    <string name="detail_mobilecustom">107448_This is a carrier-customized phone.</string>
    <string name="detail_networktimeout">107446_Network error. Please check the network and try again.</string>
    <string name="detail_repeat">107445_You submitted a testing application before. Do not submit repeated applications within 60 days.</string>
    <string name="detail_submitted">162572_Check the result after %s.</string>
    <string name="detail_timelimit">107443_This phone model does not support depth testing.</string>
    <string name="detail_wrongdata">107442_Errors in phone parameters found during verification</string>
    <string name="dialog_applying">109759_Loading... Please wait.</string>
    <string name="dialog_exittest">107434_Request to Exit Depth Testing</string>
    <string name="dialog_locktext">"107432_Are you sure you want to exit depth testing?
"</string>
    <string name="dialog_no">107431_Cancel</string>
    <string name="dialog_nonetwork">"107427_No network connection. Please check the network settings and try again.
"</string>
    <string name="dialog_ok">107430_OK</string>
    <string name="dialog_title">107429_Tips</string>
    <string name="dialog_unlocktext">"107433_Run the bootloader lock command in fastboot mode.
After the bootloader is locked, you can exit depth testing.
"</string>
    <string name="main_apply">107411_Apply Now</string>
    <string name="main_query">107414_Query Approval Status</string>
    <string name="main_title">107412_Depth Testing</string>
    <string name="main_warning">107413_The test program may have unforeseeable impacts on the phone. Users who join this test program shall bear the consequent risks by themselves.</string>
    <string name="network_timeout">107438_Network timed out.</string>
    <string name="status_ok">107421_Back</string>
    <string name="status_start">107422_Start Depth Testing</string>
    <string name="status_title">107420_Status Query</string>
    <string name="toast_submitted">107451_Your application has been submitted. Do not submit repeated applications.</string>
    <string name="verification_fail">107440_Application not approved</string>
    <string name="verification_pass">107439_Application approved</string>
    <string name="verification_submitted">107452_Application submitted for approval</string>
    <string name="warning_condition">"158408_The following conditions must be met before applying for depth testing:
1. The phone model has been released in the market for more than 3 months.
2. No application for depth testing was submitted using the same OPPO ID in the last 60 days.
3. The number of users applying for depth testing does not reach the maximum limit.
4. The phone is not an enterprise or carrier-customized phone."</string>
    <string name="warning_continue">107426_Continue Application</string>
    <string name="warning_switch">107425_Tap here to change the account to apply.</string>
    <string name="warning_title">107423_Cautions</string>
</resources>
